Very few people hike to the top of a
mountain just to know what it looks like
from the top looking down.
Most people only experience it from down
there. But if you ever come up to the
top,
you'll feel the wind. You'll see the sun
from a different angle. You'll see parts
of the rocks that you didn't know
existed. You'll pick out the flowers,
the trees, the birds, and the breeze.
You just have to bust your ass to get up
here.
And very few people have that mindset
anymore. They just want to be
comfortable. They want to be complacent.
They want to be fed. They want to laugh
and dance and sing and be happy down
there.
I think life is better lived when you
earn your man.
I busted my ass to get up here. Legs are
tired, burning, out of breath. Man, just
look at it. I feel alive, man.
I wish I had a group of friends that
like to do this too. Cuz there
ain't many of us crazy ones out here.